The way y'all are responding to the trailers for In the Man Do We Trust, it's like I don't even know if I have words yet for that emotion.
So I got to think about it because I don't know that I've ever experienced this type of emotion.
So I got to really think about it.
It is incredibly positive.
It is light bearing.
It is like changing my nervous system.
I'm going through a really rough time in my heart and my mind.
But y'all are lifting me up so high that I'm like managing it.
And I thank y'all forever for that.
In a world where deception and power rules, one brave woman answers the call of the people.
I think I'm going to run for office.
And ventures to the nation's capital to bring a trusted voice to the halls of democracy.
I mean, if I ran, do you think you would vote for me?
It depends.
Oh.
I came through because I wanted to get some insight from some folks who are already on the inside.
And, uh...
Oh, you're at first needed here.
No one is going to believe me in this.
You know what?
You never told me, what are you running for?
The question really is, what are we running to?
I'm running to the people.
Oh.
How well do you think you know government?
I went to school.
I can answer a couple questions.
How are you fighting the colonization?
Are you doing martial arts?
If I were in any office, from alderman to state senator to Republican...
Oh.
What Satan just flew into my mouth?
The Santas came in here, right?
That's what happened.
I'll act that.
In Amanda We Trust, an unapologetically political comedy doc from Amanda Seals.
Coming soon to the internet.
Hear that motorcade?
That's Kamala going home.
That could be me.
In AmandaWeTrust.com.